RG 062:085, Town of Monroe
Connecticut State Library
Town of Monroe records
1871-1974
Connecticut State Library
Monroe (Conn.)
21 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Monroe.
RG062_085
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Monroe was incorporated in May 1823 and was taken from Huntington (now Shelton).
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Monroe.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Monroe -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Monroe -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Monroe -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Monroe -- Registers
Places:
Monroe (Conn.) -- Records and Correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1871-1974
  - T000260
    - Tax abstracts
      Tax abstracts for 1911 to 1954 are not boxed.
      - 1871, 1872, 1876, 1877, 1879 (Box Box 1)
      - 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box Box 2)
      - 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 3)
      - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904 (Box Box 4)
      - 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 5)
      - 1911, 1 volume
      - 1912, 1 volume
      - 1913, 1 volume
      - 1914, 1 volume
      - 1915, 1 volume
      - 1916, 1 volume
      - 1917, 2 volumes
      - 1918, 1 volume
      - 1919, 1 volume
      - 1920, 1 volume
      - 1921, 1 volume
      - 1922, 1 volume
      - 1923, 1 volume
      - 1924, 1 volume
      - 1925, 1 volume
      - 1926, 1 volume
      - 1927, 1 volume
      - 1928, 1 volume
      - 1929, 1 volume
      - 1930, 1 volume
      - 1931, 1 volume
      - 1932, 1 volume
      - 1933, 1 volume
      - 1934, 1 volume
      - 1935, 1 volume
      - 1936, 1 volume
      - 1937, 1 volume
      - 1938, 1 volume
      - 1939, 1 volume
      - 1940, 1 volume
      - 1941, 1 volume
      - 1942, 1 volume
      - 1943, 1 volume
      - 1944, 1 volume
      - 1945, 1 volume
      - 1946, 1 volume
      - 1947, 1 volume
      - 1948, 1 volume
      - 1949, 2 volumes
      - 1950, 1 volume
      - 1951, 1 volume
      - 1952, 1 volume
      - 1953, 1 volume
      - 1954, 1 volume
  - T001166
    - Tax abstracts, 1955-1974; 20 volumes